<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ConflictOptions.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-15c36f0" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">02cd5861-7ce2-4a82-b358-31f8435a0ac5ab3cd7d259dad0e74ecfbc9e7ed7d3f48beb26c7.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">ab3cd7d259dad0e74ecfbc9e7ed7d3f48beb26c7</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">d31dc2ede16f6f7bc64e90d9f897ff54c4e3869b</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">04/03/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
      <xliffext:moniker_ids xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">netframework-4.5.1,netframework-4.5.2,netframework-4.5,netframework-4.6.1,netframework-4.6.2,netframework-4.6,netframework-4.7.1,netframework-4.7</xliffext:moniker_ids>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>Determines how ASP.NET data source controls handle data conflicts when updating or deleting data.</source>
          <target state="translated">Determina como os controles de fonte de dados do ASP.NET lida com conflitos ao atualizar ou excluir dados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>Concurrency control is a technique that data stores use to control how data is read and changed in the store when multiple clients are accessing and manipulating the same data.</source>
          <target state="translated">Controle de simultaneidade é uma técnica de repositórios de dados usam para controlar como os dados é lida e alterados no repositório quando vários clientes estão acessando e manipulando os mesmos dados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>For example, one client reads data and presents it to a user, while another client reads the same data, and presents it to a different user.</source>
          <target state="translated">Por exemplo, um cliente lê os dados e apresenta-as para um usuário, enquanto outro cliente lê os mesmos dados e apresenta-as para um usuário diferente.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>If both users update the data and submit it to the data storage, some unexpected result might occur, because the clients might update different values for the same data.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se ambos os usuários atualizam os dados e enviá-lo para o armazenamento de dados, alguns resultados inesperados poderão ocorrer, pois os clientes podem atualizar valores diferentes para os mesmos dados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>This is considered a conflict.</source>
          <target state="translated">Isso é considerado um conflito.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">`ConflictDetection`</ph> property that is defined for ASP.NET data source controls is used to determine how a control handles data conflicts in the underlying data storage when the underlying data storage is using optimistic concurrency and a delete or update operation is performed.</source>
          <target state="translated">O <ph id="ph1">`ConflictDetection`</ph> propriedade que é definida para controles de fonte de dados do ASP.NET é usada para determinar como um controle manipula conflitos de dados no armazenamento de dados subjacente quando o armazenamento de dados subjacente é usando simultaneidade otimista e uma exclusão ou operação de atualização é executada.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>By default, the <ph id="ph1">`ConflictDetection`</ph> property is set to OverwriteChanges, which means the data source control will overwrite any changes made to a data row between the time the data source control first read data from the row and the time that the row is updated.</source>
          <target state="translated">Por padrão, o <ph id="ph1">`ConflictDetection`</ph> está definida como OverwriteChanges, o que significa que o controle de fonte de dados substituirá as alterações feitas em uma linha de dados entre a hora em que o controle de fonte de dados primeiro ler dados da linha e a hora em que a linha é atualizada.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>The primary key is used for locating the data row that will be updated or deleted, but no other comparison of the data is performed.</source>
          <target state="translated">A chave primária é usada para localizar a linha de dados que será atualizada ou excluída, mas nenhuma outra comparação dos dados é executada.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>If the data source control is configured to use the CompareAllValues option, however, the control passes the original data in the <ph id="ph1">`oldValues`</ph> collections of the <ph id="ph2">`Update`</ph> and <ph id="ph3">`Delete`</ph> methods so that you can write logic to update or delete data only if these values match the values currently in the data storage.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se o controle de fonte de dados estiver configurado para usar a opção CompareAllValues, no entanto, o controle passa os dados originais no <ph id="ph1">`oldValues`</ph> coleções do <ph id="ph2">`Update`</ph> e <ph id="ph3">`Delete`</ph> métodos para que você possa escrever lógica para atualizar ou excluir dados somente se esses valores correspondem aos valores atualmente no armazenamento de dados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions">
          <source>The matching values indicate that the data has not changed since the time it was read.</source>
          <target state="translated">Os valores correspondentes indicam que os dados não foram alterados desde a hora em que foi lido.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions.CompareAllValues">
          <source>A data source control uses the <ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="oldValues" /&gt;</ph> collection of the <ph id="ph2">&lt;see langword="Update" /&gt;</ph> and <ph id="ph3">&lt;see langword="Delete" /&gt;</ph> methods to determine whether the data has been changed by another process.</source>
          <target state="translated">Um controle de fonte de dados usa a coleção <ph id="ph1">&lt;paramref name="oldValues" /&gt;</ph> dos métodos <ph id="ph2">&lt;see langword="Update" /&gt;</ph> e <ph id="ph3">&lt;see langword="Delete" /&gt;</ph> para determinar se os dados foram alterados por outro processo.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.Web.UI.ConflictOptions.OverwriteChanges">
          <source>A data source control overwrites all values in a data row with its own values for the row.</source>
          <target state="translated">Um controle de fonte de dados substitui todos os valores em uma linha de dados com seus próprios valores para a linha.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>