<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.Web.Services.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef186424dfb8ce40482314b15af5fd8853c9af3a311cc2.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">24dfb8ce40482314b15af5fd8853c9af3a311cc2</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Web.Services" /&gt;</ph> namespace consists of the classes that enable you to create XML Web services using ASP.NET and XML Web service clients.</source>
          <target state="translated">O namespace <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Web.Services" /&gt;</ph> consiste em classes que permitem que você crie serviços Web XML usando clientes de serviço Web XML e ASP.NET.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>XML Web services are applications that provide the ability to exchange messages in a loosely coupled environment using standard protocols such as HTTP, XML, XSD, SOAP, and WSDL.</source>
          <target state="translated">Os serviços Web XML são aplicativos permitem a troca de mensagens em um ambiente fracamente acoplado usando protocolos padrão como HTTP, XML, XSD, SOAP e WSDL.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>XML Web services enable the building of modular applications within and across companies in heterogeneous environments making them interoperable with a broad variety of implementations, platforms and devices.</source>
          <target state="translated">Os serviços Web XML permitem a criação de aplicativos modulares dentro e entre empresas em ambientes heterogêneos, tornando-os e interoperáveis com uma ampla variedade de implementações, plataformas e dispositivos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The SOAP-based XML messages of these applications can have well-defined (structured and typed), or loosely defined parts (using arbitrary XML).</source>
          <target state="translated">As mensagens XML baseadas em SOAP desses aplicativos podem ter partes bem definidas (estruturadas e tipadas) ou pouco definidas (usando XML arbitrário).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The ability of the messages to evolve over time without breaking the protocol is fundamental to the flexibility and robustness of XML Web services as a building block for the future of the Web.</source>
          <target state="translated">A capacidade das mensagens de evoluir ao longo do tempo sem quebrar o protocolo é fundamental para a flexibilidade e a robustez dos serviços Web XML como um bloco de construção para o futuro da Web.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>To get started creating XML Web services using ASP.NET, look at the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Web.Services.WebService&gt;</ph> class, which XML Web services can derive from to get access to the ASP.NET intrinsics and the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Web.Services.WebMethodAttribute&gt;</ph> class, which must be placed on any method that you want to programmatically expose over the Web.</source>
          <target state="translated">Para começar a criar serviços Web XML usando o ASP.NET, examine o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Web.Services.WebService&gt;</ph> classe, quais serviços Web XML podem derivar de obter acesso a intrínsecos do ASP.NET e o <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Web.Services.WebMethodAttribute&gt;</ph> classe, que deve ser colocado em qualquer método que você deseja expor por meio de programação através da Web.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>