<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864a8760d09a78e9a2fbe294d04c88c1e7efe895792.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">a8760d09a78e9a2fbe294d04c88c1e7efe895792</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /&gt;</ph> namespace contains classes that support and handle channels and channel sinks, which are used as the transport medium when a client calls a method on a remote object.</source>
          <target state="translated">O namespace <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /&gt;</ph> contém classes que oferecem suporte e lidam com canais e coletores de canal, que são usados como o meio de transporte quando um cliente chama um método em um objeto remoto.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Channels are objects that transport messages between applications across remoting boundaries, whether between application domains, processes, or computers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Canais são objetos que as mensagens de transporte entre os aplicativos em limites de comunicação remota entre domínios de aplicativo, processos ou computadores.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>A channel can listen on an endpoint for inbound messages, send outbound messages to another endpoint, or both.</source>
          <target state="translated">Um canal pode escutar em um ponto de extremidade de mensagens de entrada, enviar mensagens de saída para outro ponto de extremidade, ou ambos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>This enables you to plug in a wide range of protocols, even if the common language runtime is not at the other end of the channel.</source>
          <target state="translated">Isso permite que você conecte uma ampla variedade de protocolos, mesmo que o common language runtime não está na outra extremidade do canal.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Channels send each object along a chain of channel sink objects prior to sending or after receiving a message.</source>
          <target state="translated">Canais de enviar cada objeto ao longo de uma cadeia de objetos de coletor de canal antes de enviar ou depois de receber uma mensagem.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>This sink chain contains sinks required for basic channel functionality, such as transport or stack builder sinks, but you can customize the channel sink chain to perform special tasks with a message or a stream.</source>
          <target state="translated">Esta cadeia de coletor contém coletores necessárias para a funcionalidade básica de canal, como o transporte ou a pilha de Coletores de construtor, mas você pode personalizar a cadeia de coletor de canal para realizar tarefas especiais com uma mensagem ou um fluxo.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Each sink in each chain receives the object, performs a specific operation, and passes it on to the next sink in the chain.</source>
          <target state="translated">Cada coletor em cada cadeia recebe o objeto, executa uma operação específica e passa para o coletor Avançar na cadeia.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>There is no rule that the exact object received by a message sink must be passed on to the next sink, though this will often be the case.</source>
          <target state="translated">Não há nenhuma regra que o objeto exato recebido por um coletor de mensagem deve ser passado para o coletor de Avançar, embora isso geralmente será o caso.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>For more information, see <bpt id="p1">[</bpt>Channels<ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18)</ept> and <bpt id="p2">[</bpt>Sinks and Sink Chains<ept id="p2">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)</ept>.</source>
          <target state="translated">Para obter mais informações, consulte <bpt id="p1">[</bpt>canais<ept id="p1">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18)</ept> e <bpt id="p2">[</bpt>coletores e cadeias de coletor<ept id="p2">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)</ept>.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>