<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.Net.PeerToPeer.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864320f5d11742848ae51a1bbb18f46ae6b439a5235.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">320f5d11742848ae51a1bbb18f46ae6b439a5235</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /&gt;</ph> namespace provides access to peer networking functionality.</source>
          <target state="translated">O namespace <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /&gt;</ph> fornece acesso à funcionalidade de rede de par.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>How peers discover each other and resolve identifiers is complicated by transient connectivity and the lack of access to address records such as the Domain Name System (DNS).</source>
          <target state="translated">Como pares de descobrem uns aos outros e resolver os identificadores é complicado devido a falta de acesso a registros de endereços como sistema de nome de domínio (DNS) e de conectividade transitória.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The Windows Peer-to-Peer Infrastructure solves this problem with a name resolution and peer discovery scheme called PNRP.</source>
          <target state="translated">A infraestrutura de ponto a ponto do Windows resolve esse problema com um nome correspondente e resolução descoberta esquema chamado PNRP.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Peer Name Resolution Protocol (PNRP) provides a name resolution mechanism for peer-to-peer networks.</source>
          <target state="translated">Resolução de protocolo PNRP (Peer Name) fornece um mecanismo de resolução de nome para redes ponto a ponto.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>PNRP is designed to resolve a name to a network <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint&gt;</ph> in a completely peer-to-peer manner.</source>
          <target state="translated">O PNRP foi projetado para resolver um nome para uma rede <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint&gt;</ph> de maneira completamente ponto a ponto.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Basic PNRP functionality is provided in the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer&gt;</ph> namespace classes.</source>
          <target state="translated">A funcionalidade básica do protocolo PNRP é fornecida no <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer&gt;</ph> classes do namespace.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>They provide the ability to create a peer and register it in a <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud&gt;</ph> of peers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Eles fornecem a capacidade de criar um par e registrá-lo em um <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud&gt;</ph> de pares.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>They also provide the ability to resolve a <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName&gt;</ph> to its network endpoint, TCP port, cloud, or other address identifier(s).</source>
          <target state="translated">Eles também fornecem a capacidade de resolver um <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName&gt;</ph> para seu ponto de extremidade de rede, porta TCP, nuvem ou outros identificadores de endereço.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Advanced functionality for peer-to-peer networking is provided in the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration&gt;</ph> namespace.</source>
          <target state="translated">Recursos avançados para rede ponto a ponto é fornecido no <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration&gt;</ph> namespace.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>In Windows Vista, PNRP ships as a service that is started on demand by applications.</source>
          <target state="translated">No Windows Vista, PNRP é fornecido como um serviço que é iniciado sob demanda por aplicativos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service that can be manually enabled by applications or users if they want to publish machine names for remote connections and communications.</source>
          <target state="translated">Além disso, há um serviço de registro de máquina PNRP que pode ser habilitado manualmente por aplicativos ou usuários se deseja publicar os nomes de computador para conexões remotas e comunicações.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>PNRP version 1 was included in Windows XP Service Pack 2 (SP2), Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, and Windows XP with Service Pack 1 (SP1) and the Advanced Networking Pack for Windows XP.</source>
          <target state="translated">O PNRP versão 1 foi incluído no Windows XP com Service Pack 1 (SP1) e o pacote de rede avançado para o Windows XP, Windows XP Professional x64 Edition e Windows XP Service Pack 2 (SP2).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="113" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service which can be manually enabled by applications/users if there is interest in publishing machine names for remote connection and communication.</source>
          <target state="translated">Além disso, há um serviço de registro de máquina PNRP que pode ser habilitado manualmente por usuários/aplicativos se houver interesse em publicação nomes de computador para comunicação e conexão remota.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>