<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864b482f98a5c4316a191cd9beb8d2d226874520920.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">b482f98a5c4316a191cd9beb8d2d226874520920</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /&gt;</ph> namespace provides support for authentication using extended protection for applications.</source>
          <target state="translated">O namespace <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /&gt;</ph> dá suporte à autenticação usando proteção estendida para aplicativos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The design of Integrated Windows Authentication (IWA) allows for some credential challenge responses to be universal, meaning they can be re-used or forwarded.</source>
          <target state="translated">O design do Windows IWA (autenticação integrada) permite que algumas respostas de desafio de credencial ser universal, o que significa que podem ser usados novamente ou encaminhadas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>If this particular design feature is not needed then the challenge responses should be constructed with, at minimum, target specific information and, at best, also some channel specific information.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se esse recurso de design específico não for necessária, em seguida, o desafio respostas devem ser construído com, no mínimo, informações específicas do destino e, na melhor das hipóteses, também algumas canal informações específicas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Services can then provide extended protection to ensure that credential challenge responses contain service specific information (a Service Provider Name or SPN) and, if necessary, channel specific information (a channel binding token or CBT).</source>
          <target state="translated">Serviços, em seguida, podem fornecer proteção estendida para garantir que as respostas de desafio de credencial contêm informações específicas do serviço (um nome de provedor de serviço ou SPN) e, se necessário, canal específicas informações (um token de associação de canal ou CBT).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>With this information in the credential exchanges, services are able to better protect against malicious use of credential challenge responses that might have been improperly obtained.</source>
          <target state="translated">Com essas informações em trocas de credencial, os serviços são capazes de melhor proteção contra o uso de respostas de desafio de credencial que pode ter sido obtido incorretamente.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>