<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ns-System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-efd8310" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">5a83ea4b-dd12-480b-bfc8-267272ef1864fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">05/10/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> namespace provides uniform access and manipulation of user, computer, and group security principals across the multiple principal stores: Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM).</source>
          <target state="translated">O namespace <ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> fornece acesso uniforme e manipulação de entidades de segurança de grupo, computador e usuário nos vários repositórios de entidade de segurança: AD DS (Active Directory Domain Services), AD LDS (Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services) e MSAM (Machine SAM).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve">
          <source><ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> manages directory objects independent of the <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /&gt;</ph> namespace.</source>
          <target state="translated"><ph id="ph1">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /&gt;</ph> gerencia objetos de diretório independentemente do namespace <ph id="ph2">&lt;see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /&gt;</ph>.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Managed directory services applications can take advantage of the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API to simplify management of user, computer and group principals.</source>
          <target state="translated">Aplicativos de serviços de diretório gerenciado podem aproveitar o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API para simplificar o gerenciamento de usuário, computador e grupo de entidades.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Solutions that previously required intricate knowledge of the store or lengthy code, such as finding all groups to which a user belongs, are accomplished in a few lines of code with the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API.</source>
          <target state="translated">Soluções que previamente necessitaram de conhecimento profundo do armazenamento ou código longo, como localizar todos os grupos aos quais um usuário pertence, são realizadas em algumas linhas de código com o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The following features are available on the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API:</source>
          <target state="translated">Os seguintes recursos estão disponíveis no <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement&gt;</ph> API:</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Basic directory operations such as creating and updating security principals is simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Operações básicas do diretório, como criação e atualização de entidades de segurança é simplificado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>The application requires less knowledge of the underlying stores to perform these operations.</source>
          <target state="translated">O aplicativo requer menos conhecimento das lojas subjacentes para executar essas operações.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Applications can extend the object model to include new types of directory objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">Aplicativos podem estender o modelo de objeto para incluir novos tipos de objetos de diretório.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Account management tasks, such as enabling and disabling a user account, are simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Tarefas de gerenciamento de conta, como habilitar e desabilitar uma conta de usuário são simplificadas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Cross-store support allows group objects in the Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM) databases to contain members from different types of stores.</source>
          <target state="translated">Suporte entre armazenamentos permite que os objetos de grupo nos serviços de domínio Active Directory (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS) e bancos de dados do SAM do computador (MSAM) para conter membros de diferentes tipos de armazenamentos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Query by example searching, available on the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher&gt;</ph> class, enables applications to set properties on a principal object and search the selected store for other objects that contain matching property values.</source>
          <target state="translated">Consulta por meio de pesquisa de exemplo, disponível na <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher&gt;</ph> classe permite que os aplicativos para definir propriedades em um objeto principal e procure outros objetos que contêm valores de propriedade correspondentes na loja selecionada.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Enhanced search on computer, user and group principal objects enables applications to search the selected store for matching principal objects.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pesquisa avançada no computador, usuário e objetos de grupo permite que os aplicativos procurar o repositório selecionado para correspondência de objetos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="113" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Recursive search, available on the group principal object, enables applications to search a group recursively and return only principal objects that are leaf nodes.</source>
          <target state="translated">Pesquisa recursiva, disponível no objeto principal do grupo, permite que os aplicativos pesquisar uma grupo de forma recursiva e retornar apenas os objetos principais que são nós folha.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="114" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Credential validation against the Machine SAM, AD DS, and AD LS stores is simplified.</source>
          <target state="translated">Validação de credenciais contra os repositórios de computador SAM, AD DS e AD LS é simplificada.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="115" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Connections speeds are increased by using the Fast Concurrent Bind (FSB) feature when available.</source>
          <target state="translated">Velocidades de conexões são aumentadas usando o recurso Fast simultâneas associar (frontal) quando disponível.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="116" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT">
          <source>Connection caching decreases the number of ports used.</source>
          <target state="translated">Conexão de cache diminui o número de portas usadas.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>