<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="SupportedAddressingMode.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-15c36f0" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">02cd5861-7ce2-4a82-b358-31f8435a0ac52e96bbd9b4b430691aed6a16a4a3b6015bec77b8.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">2e96bbd9b4b430691aed6a16a4a3b6015bec77b8</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">d31dc2ede16f6f7bc64e90d9f897ff54c4e3869b</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">04/03/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
      <xliffext:moniker_ids xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">netframework-4.5.1,netframework-4.5.2,netframework-4.5,netframework-4.6.1,netframework-4.6.2,netframework-4.6,netframework-4.7.1,netframework-4.7,xamarinandroid-7.1,xamarinios-10.8,xamarinmac-3.0</xliffext:moniker_ids>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Specifies whether a service supports sending responses to anonymous addresses only, to non-anonymous addresses only, or to both.</source>
          <target state="translated">Especifica se um serviço dá suporte ao envio de respostas a apenas endereços anônimos, a apenas endereços não anônimos ou a ambos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>This enumeration is used to specify the capability of a server, which, in turn, imposes a requirement on its clients.</source>
          <target state="translated">Essa enumeração é usada para especificar a capacidade de um servidor, que, por sua vez, impõe uma necessidade em seus clientes.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source><ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo1](~/includes/indigo1-md.md)]</ph> has a variety of addressing controls for specifying where messages should be sent.</source>
          <target state="translated"><ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo1](~/includes/indigo1-md.md)]</ph> tem uma variedade de controles de endereçamento para especificar onde as mensagens devem ser enviadas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>For example, there is the logical <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.MessageHeaders.To%2A&gt;</ph> address for the message destination, the physical ("Via") address, used by the transport, at which a service listens, and the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.MessageHeaders.ReplyTo%2A&gt;</ph> address of the endpoint that provides the address of the client endpoint.</source>
          <target state="translated">Por exemplo, há lógico <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.MessageHeaders.To%2A&gt;</ph> endereço para o destino da mensagem, físico endereço, usado pelo transporte, em que um serviço de escuta, ("Via") e o <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.MessageHeaders.ReplyTo%2A&gt;</ph> endereço do ponto de extremidade que fornece o endereço do ponto de extremidade do cliente.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>In the most basic case, when two parties exchange messages between themselves only, it is not necessary to specify these addresses separately.</source>
          <target state="translated">No caso mais básico, quando duas partes da trocam de mensagens entre si só, não é necessário especificar esses endereços separadamente.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>But because exchanges can involve other message destinations, you must be able to specify when addresses must be explicitly provided.</source>
          <target state="translated">Mas como trocas podem envolver outros destinos de mensagens, você deve ser capaz de especificar quando os endereços devem ser fornecidos explicitamente.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Even between just two parties this ability is sometimes required, as with dual HTTP where the server must create its own HTTP request.</source>
          <target state="translated">Até mesmo entre apenas duas partes essa capacidade às vezes é necessária, como com HTTP dupla onde o servidor deve criar sua própria solicitação HTTP.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>The following kinds of relationships are defined by the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode&gt;</ph> enumeration to capture these messaging patterns:</source>
          <target state="translated">Os seguintes tipos de relações são definidos pelo <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode&gt;</ph> enumeração para capturar esses padrões de mensagens:</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Anonymous addresses are the most basic form of addressing.</source>
          <target state="translated">Endereços anônimos são a forma mais básica de endereçamento.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Anonymous addressing is used when there is a default path for a response.</source>
          <target state="translated">Endereçamento anônima é usada quando há um caminho padrão para uma resposta.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>TCP is a bi-directional communication transport and the response to a TCP message can be sent back to the other side of the socket that sent the original message.</source>
          <target state="translated">O TCP é um transporte de comunicação bidirecional e a resposta a uma mensagem TCP pode ser enviada para o outro lado do soquete que enviou a mensagem original.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Similarly, the request-reply model of HTTP sends responses through the HTTP reply channel.</source>
          <target state="translated">Da mesma forma, o modelo de solicitação-resposta de HTTP envia respostas por meio do canal de resposta HTTP.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="113" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Neither of these responses requires specifying where the response messages are going.</source>
          <target state="translated">Nenhuma dessas respostas requer a especificação de onde as mensagens de resposta serão.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="114" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>When a server requires anonymous responses from the client, it uses the Anonymous value of the enumeration.</source>
          <target state="translated">Quando um servidor requer anônimas respostas do cliente, ele usa o valor anônimo da enumeração.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="115" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo2](~/includes/indigo2-md.md)]</ph> system-provided <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.NetTcpBinding&gt;</ph>, <ph id="ph3">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.BasicHttpBinding&gt;</ph> and <ph id="ph4">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.WSHttpBinding&gt;</ph> bindings always use Anonymous addresses.</source>
          <target state="translated">O <ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo2](~/includes/indigo2-md.md)]</ph> fornecido pelo sistema <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.NetTcpBinding&gt;</ph>, <ph id="ph3">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.BasicHttpBinding&gt;</ph> e <ph id="ph4">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.WSHttpBinding&gt;</ph> associações sempre usam endereços anônimos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="116" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>NonAnonymous addresses are used when sending the response requires creating a new channel for communication.</source>
          <target state="translated">Endereços não anônimos são usados ao enviar a resposta requer a criação de um novo canal de comunicação.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="117" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo2](~/includes/indigo2-md.md)]</ph> system-provided <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.WSDualHttpBinding&gt;</ph> binding uses a NonAnonymous address.</source>
          <target state="translated">O <ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo2](~/includes/indigo2-md.md)]</ph> fornecido pelo sistema <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.WSDualHttpBinding&gt;</ph> associação usa um endereço não anônimos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="118" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>With dual HTTP, the client creates an HTTP request to send a message and then the server must create its own HTTP request to send a response.</source>
          <target state="translated">Com dois HTTP, o cliente cria uma solicitação HTTP para enviar uma mensagem e, em seguida, o servidor deve criar sua própria solicitação HTTP para enviar uma resposta.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="119" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Because the server is initiating the send, it must have a specific endpoint to establish the connection.</source>
          <target state="translated">Porque o servidor está iniciando o envio, ele deve ter um ponto de extremidade específico para estabelecer a conexão.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="120" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>You must provide the server the address of an endpoint for its response.</source>
          <target state="translated">Você deve fornecer o endereço de um ponto de extremidade do servidor para sua resposta.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="121" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Similarly, if a service must respond to a one-way message that it received, it also requires a NonAnonymous address because there is no back channel available for communication.</source>
          <target state="translated">Da mesma forma, se um serviço deve responder a uma mensagem unidirecional que recebeu, ele também requer um não anônimos endereço porque não há nenhum canal de retorno disponível para comunicação.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="122" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>If the server sends a message back, a completely separate operation from that used to send the first message is required.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se o servidor envia uma mensagem, é necessária uma operação completamente separada daquele usado para enviar a primeira mensagem.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="123" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>Mixed is a third form of addressing which combines Anonymous and NonAnonymous addresses depending on the message that is being sent.</source>
          <target state="translated">Misto é uma terceira forma de endereçamento que combina endereços anônimo e não anônimos, dependendo da mensagem que está sendo enviado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="124" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>A typical example of mixed-mode addressing is the use of a dedicated machine for processing fault or acknowledgment messages.</source>
          <target state="translated">Um exemplo típico de endereçamento de modo misto é o uso de um computador dedicado para processamento de mensagens de confirmação ou de falha.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="125" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>If the standard exchange sequence for replies is HTTP or TCP, the responses use Anonymous addressing but the faults use non-anonymous addressing.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se a sequência padrão do exchange para respostas HTTP ou TCP, as respostas usam endereçamento anônima mas as falhas usam endereçamento não anônimas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="126" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>While <ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo2](~/includes/indigo2-md.md)]</ph> does not provide Mixed addressing functionality in one of its standard bindings, it is possible to write a channel that allows the service to send responses directly on the back-channel (when the response address is Anonymous) or on a separate channel (when the response address is NonAnonymous).</source>
          <target state="translated">Enquanto <ph id="ph1">[!INCLUDE[indigo2](~/includes/indigo2-md.md)]</ph> não fornece Mixed abordar a funcionalidade de uma das suas associações padrão, é possível gravar um canal que permite que o serviço enviar respostas diretamente no back-channel (quando o endereço de resposta é anônimo) ou em um canal separado (quando o endereço de resposta não anônimos).</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="127" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode">
          <source>In such a case, the binding element of the channel is used to set <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode&gt;</ph> to Mixed.</source>
          <target state="translated">Nesse caso, o elemento de associação do canal é usado para definir <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode&gt;</ph> como Mixed.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="128" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode.Anonymous">
          <source>The server only supports anonymous addresses and clients must provide an anonymous response address.</source>
          <target state="translated">O servidor só dá suporte a endereços anônimos e os clientes devem fornecer um endereço de resposta anônimo.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="129" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode.Mixed">
          <source>The server supports both anonymous and non-anonymous addresses and clients may choose to use either or both.</source>
          <target state="translated">O servidor dá suporte a endereços anônimos e não anônimos e os clientes podem optar por usar um deles ou ambos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="130" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.ServiceModel.Channels.SupportedAddressingMode.NonAnonymous">
          <source>The server only supports non-anonymous addresses and clients must provide a non-anonymous response address.</source>
          <target state="translated">O servidor só dá suporte a endereços não anônimos e os clientes devem fornecer um endereço de resposta não anônimo.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>