<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="TransferSession.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-15c36f0" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">02cd5861-7ce2-4a82-b358-31f8435a0ac57b757f09be52ab6f8895488cf7a3f7be347618a8.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">7b757f09be52ab6f8895488cf7a3f7be347618a8</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">d31dc2ede16f6f7bc64e90d9f897ff54c4e3869b</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">04/03/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
      <xliffext:moniker_ids xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">netframework-4.5.1,netframework-4.5.2,netframework-4.5,netframework-4.6.1,netframework-4.6.2,netframework-4.6,netframework-4.7.1,netframework-4.7,xamarinandroid-7.1,xamarinios-10.8,xamarinmac-3.0</xliffext:moniker_ids>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>Determines if the contract for the transfer of messages from a client to an application requires a session and whether the delivery of messages must preserve the order in which operations are called by the client.</source>
          <target state="translated">Determina se o contrato para a transferência de mensagens de um cliente para um aplicativo requer uma sessão e se a entrega de mensagens deve preservar a ordem na qual as operações são chamadas pelo cliente.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession&gt;</ph> enumerations are typically used in association with a service contract.</source>
          <target state="translated">O <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession&gt;</ph> as enumerações são geralmente usadas em associação com um contrato de serviço.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>When a client sends messages to a remote application or service to call operations, <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession&gt;</ph> is used to determine if a session is required to interact with the service and whether the messages used to invoke the operations at a service must arrive in the same order in which they were sent.</source>
          <target state="translated">Quando um cliente envia mensagens para um aplicativo remoto ou o serviço para chamar operações, <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession&gt;</ph> é usado para determinar se uma sessão é necessária para interagir com o serviço e se as mensagens usadas para invocar as operações em um serviço devem chegar na mesma ordem em que foram enviadas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>Message delivery between client and service requires a session to preserve the order in which operations are called by the client.</source>
          <target state="translated">Entrega de mensagens entre cliente e serviço requer uma sessão para preservar a ordem na qual as operações são chamadas pelo cliente.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>If there is no session between endpoints, then the delivery order does not reflect the order in which the messages are sent.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se não houver nenhuma sessão entre pontos de extremidade, a ordem de entrega não reflete a ordem na qual as mensagens são enviadas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>The value of <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession&gt;</ph> that an application uses specifies whether the application requires a specific order in the calling sequence.</source>
          <target state="translated">O valor de <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession&gt;</ph> que um aplicativo usa Especifica se o aplicativo requer uma ordem específica na sequência de chamada.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>If Ordered, then the contract requires that messages must arrive in the order in which they are sent.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se forem solicitados, o contrato requer que as mensagens devem chegar na ordem em que são enviados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>If Unordered, then the messages used to invoke public operations can arrive in any order.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se desordenadas, em seguida, as mensagens usadas para invocar operações públicas podem chegar em qualquer ordem.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession">
          <source>If None, there are no sessions.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se não houver nenhum, não existem sessões.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession.None">
          <source>Specifies that a session is not required to interact with the services on this contract.</source>
          <target state="translated">Especifica que uma sessão não é necessário para interagir com os serviços nesse contrato.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession.Ordered">
          <source>Specifies that a session with ordered message delivery guarantees is required to interact with the services on this contract.</source>
          <target state="translated">Especifica que uma sessão com garantias de entrega ordenada de mensagem é necessária para interagir com os serviços nesse contrato.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="F:System.ServiceModel.Channels.TransferSession.Unordered">
          <source>Specifies that a session with unordered message delivery guarantees is sufficient to interact with the services on this contract.</source>
          <target state="translated">Especifica que uma sessão com garantias de entrega de mensagem não ordenada é suficiente para interagir com os serviços nesse contrato.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>