<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<xliff xmlns="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="1.2" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2 xliff-core-1.2-transitional.xsd">
  <file datatype="xml" original="ProfileOptimization.xml" source-language="en-US" target-language="pt-BR">
    <header>
      <tool tool-id="mdxliff" tool-name="mdxliff" tool-version="1.0-15c36f0" tool-company="Microsoft" />
      <xliffext:skl_file_name xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">02cd5861-7ce2-4a82-b358-31f8435a0ac5bd86c9e8585771817dff9c403cde415163613389.skl</xliffext:skl_file_name>
      <xliffext:version xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">1.2</xliffext:version>
      <xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">bd86c9e8585771817dff9c403cde415163613389</xliffext:ms.openlocfilehash>
      <xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">d31dc2ede16f6f7bc64e90d9f897ff54c4e3869b</xliffext:ms.sourcegitcommit>
      <xliffext:ms.lasthandoff xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">04/03/2018</xliffext:ms.lasthandoff>
      <xliffext:moniker_ids xmlns:xliffext="urn:microsoft:content:schema:xliffextensions">netframework-4.5.1,netframework-4.5.2,netframework-4.5,netframework-4.6.1,netframework-4.6.2,netframework-4.6,netframework-4.7.1,netframework-4.7</xliffext:moniker_ids>
    </header>
    <body>
      <group id="content" extype="content">
        <trans-unit id="101" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>Improves the startup performance of application domains in applications that require the just-in-time (JIT) compiler by performing background compilation of methods that are likely to be executed, based on profiles created during previous compilations.</source>
          <target state="translated">Melhora o desempenho de inicialização de domínios do aplicativo em aplicativos que exigem o compilador JIT (Just-In-Time), executando a compilação em segundo plano dos métodos que provavelmente serão executados, com base nos perfis criados durante as compilações anteriores.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="102" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>Profile optimization requires a multicore computer.</source>
          <target state="translated">Otimização de perfil requer um computador com vários núcleos.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="103" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>The methods are ignored on other computers.</source>
          <target state="translated">Os métodos são ignorados em outros computadores.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="104" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>Each time you initiate profile optimization in an application domain, the profile that was created during the previous use is read.</source>
          <target state="translated">Cada vez que você inicia a otimização de perfil em um domínio de aplicativo, o perfil que foi criado durante o uso anterior é lido.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="105" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>The information in the profile is used to guide background compilation by identifying the methods that are most likely to be executed during startup.</source>
          <target state="translated">As informações do perfil são usadas para orientar a compilação em segundo plano, identificando os métodos que têm mais probabilidade de ser executado durante a inicialização.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="106" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>On multicore computers, this increases the chances that a method is already compiled by the time it is needed so that the main application thread does not have to call the JIT compiler.</source>
          <target state="translated">Em computadores com vários núcleos, isso aumenta as chances de que um método já compilados pelo tempo necessário para que o thread principal do aplicativo não precisa chamar o compilador JIT.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="107" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>The profile file is overwritten on each use, so it always contains the most recent information about which methods are used during startup.</source>
          <target state="translated">O arquivo de perfil é substituído cada uso, assim ele sempre contém as informações mais recentes sobre quais métodos são usados durante a inicialização.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="108" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>Optimization profiles are not restricted to application domain startup.</source>
          <target state="translated">Perfis de otimização não estão restritos a inicialização do domínio de aplicativo.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="109" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>They can be used for any activity that will require heavy use of the JIT compiler.</source>
          <target state="translated">Eles podem ser usados para qualquer atividade que exigirá o uso intenso do compilador JIT.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="110" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>You can maintain multiple profiles for an application domain so that each such activity has its own profile.</source>
          <target state="translated">Você pode manter vários perfis para um domínio de aplicativo para que cada essa atividade tem seu próprio perfil.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="111" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>To use optimization profiles in an application domain, you must call the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> method and specify the folder where profiles are stored.</source>
          <target state="translated">Para usar perfis de otimização em um domínio de aplicativo, você deve chamar o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> método e especifique a pasta onde os perfis são armazenados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="112" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>The folder must already exist.</source>
          <target state="translated">A pasta já deve existir.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="113" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>To begin using a profile, call the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> method and specify the file name of the profile.</source>
          <target state="translated">Para começar a usar um perfil, chame o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> método e especifique o nome do arquivo do perfil.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="114" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>If the file was not recorded previously, it is created on first use.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se o arquivo não foi gravado anteriormente, ele será criado no primeiro uso.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="115" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>There is no performance benefit the first time a profile is created.</source>
          <target state="translated">Não há nenhum tempo de primeiro do benefício de desempenho um perfil é criado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="116" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>Profile optimization does not change the order in which methods are executed.</source>
          <target state="translated">Otimização de perfil não altera a ordem na qual os métodos são executados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="117" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>Methods are not executed on the background thread; if a method is compiled but never called, it is simply not used.</source>
          <target state="translated">Métodos não são executados no thread em segundo plano; Se um método é compilado, mas nunca foi chamado, ele simplesmente não será usado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="118" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="T:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization">
          <source>If a profile file is corrupt or cannot be written to the specified folder (for example, because the folder does not exist), program execution continues without optimization profiling.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se um arquivo de perfil está corrompido ou não pode ser gravado na pasta especificada (por exemplo, porque a pasta não existe), a execução do programa continua sem otimização de criação de perfil.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="119" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>The full path to the folder where profile files are stored for the current application domain.</source>
          <target state="translated">O caminho completo para a pasta na qual os arquivos de perfil são armazenados para o domínio de aplicativo atual.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="120" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>Enables optimization profiling for the current application domain, and sets the folder where the optimization profile files are stored.</source>
          <target state="translated">Permite a criação de perfil de otimização para o domínio de aplicativo atual de otimização e define a pasta na qual os arquivos de perfil de otimização são armazenados.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="121" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>On a single-core computer, the method is ignored.</source>
          <target state="translated">Em um computador de núcleo único, o método é ignorado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="122" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>You must call this method before you call the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> method for the first time in the current application domain.</source>
          <target state="translated">Você deve chamar esse método antes de chamar o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> método pela primeira vez no domínio do aplicativo atual.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="123" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>If you call <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> more than once in the same application domain, all calls after the first are ignored.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se você chamar <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> mais de uma vez no mesmo domínio de aplicativo, todas as chamadas feitas depois do primeiro serão ignoradas.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="124" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>The specified folder must already exist.</source>
          <target state="translated">A pasta especificada já deve existir.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="125" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>If it does not exist, calling this method does not create it, and no profiling occurs.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se não existir, chamar este método não criá-lo e nenhuma criação de perfil ocorre.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="126" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>On computers that do not have multiple cores, this method is ignored.</source>
          <target state="translated">Em computadores que não têm vários núcleos, esse método é ignorado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="127" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>requires full trust for the immediate caller.</source>
          <target state="translated">requer confiança total para o chamador imediato.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="128" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot(System.String)">
          <source>This member cannot be used by partially trusted or transparent code.</source>
          <target state="translated">Este membro não pode ser usado pelo código transparente ou parcialmente confiável.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="129" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>The file name of the profile to use.</source>
          <target state="translated">O nome de arquivo do perfil a ser usado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="130" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>Starts just-in-time (JIT) compilation of the methods that were previously recorded in the specified profile file, on a background thread.</source>
          <target state="translated">Inicia a compilação JIT (Just-In-Time) dos métodos que foram registrados anteriormente no arquivo de perfil especificado em um thread em segundo plano.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="131" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>Starts the process of recording current method use, which later overwrites the specified profile file.</source>
          <target state="translated">Inicia o processo de gravação do uso do método atual, que posteriormente substituirá o arquivo de perfil especificado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="132" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>If the specified profile exists in the folder specified by the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> method, the information it contains is used to determine the order in which methods are compiled on the background thread.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se o perfil especificado existe na pasta especificada o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> método, as informações que ele contém é usado para determinar a ordem na qual os métodos são compilados no thread em segundo plano.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="133" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>The <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> method creates the profile if it does not already exist, and initiates the recording of method use.</source>
          <target state="translated">O <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> método cria o perfil, se ainda não existir e inicia o registro de uso do método.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="134" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>Only methods that are actually called are recorded, regardless of whether they were compiled on the background thread or on the main application thread.</source>
          <target state="translated">Somente os métodos que são chamados, na verdade, são registrados, independentemente se eles foram compilados no thread em segundo plano ou no thread principal do aplicativo.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="135" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>A method is compiled on the main application thread if the application needs to call it before the background thread has compiled it.</source>
          <target state="translated">Um método é compilado no thread principal do aplicativo se o aplicativo precisa chamá-lo antes do thread em segundo plano compilou.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="136" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>The code that performs the recording tracks the rate at which methods are compiled, including methods that are compiled on both the background thread and on the main thread.</source>
          <target state="translated">O código que executa a gravação rastreia a taxa em que os métodos são compilados, incluindo métodos que são compilados no thread de segundo plano e no thread principal.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="137" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>When the rate falls below a predetermined level, recording stops.</source>
          <target state="translated">Quando a taxa cai abaixo de um nível predeterminado, gravação interrompe.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="138" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>Recording also stops if the rate of JIT compilation exceeds a predetermined upper limit.</source>
          <target state="translated">Gravação também parará se a taxa de compilação JIT excede um limite predeterminado.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="139" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>If the <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> method has not been called for the current application domain, or if the computer does not have multiple cores, the <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> method has no effect.</source>
          <target state="translated">Se o <ph id="ph1">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.SetProfileRoot%2A&gt;</ph> método não foi chamado para o domínio de aplicativo atual, ou se o computador não tiver vários núcleos, o <ph id="ph2">&lt;xref:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile%2A&gt;</ph> método não tem nenhum efeito.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="140" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>requires full trust for the immediate caller.</source>
          <target state="translated">requer confiança total para o chamador imediato.</target>       </trans-unit>
        <trans-unit id="141" translate="yes" xml:space="preserve" extradata="MT" uid="M:System.Runtime.ProfileOptimization.StartProfile(System.String)">
          <source>This member cannot be used by partially trusted or transparent code.</source>
          <target state="translated">Este membro não pode ser usado pelo código transparente ou parcialmente confiável.</target>       </trans-unit>
      </group>
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>